

About me

I am a young woman of 26 years old who loved animation. Since I am a child I have dreamt to create and develop stories which beyond the screen. I want to increase not only my knowldege and abilities as animator but also to grown as a person. I want to share my skills to others and also to learn the things that team work can give me

More information

- Driving license tipe B
- Total availability

Contact

+34 689 17 14 50

patriciaidoate@gmail.com

Spain

https://vimeo.com/758018160

PATRICIA IDOATE

3D Character Animator

Work experience

Fixer Animator

Mago Production (Barcelona) | May 2024 - At the moment

- Fixing animations on the 3D film The light of Aisha
- Publication and rendering the shots of the 3D film The light of Aisha

Fixer Animator

B-Water (Barcelona) | Febraury 2023 - March 2024

- Fixing animations on the TV series Klincus and Dinomite
- Publication and rendering the shots of the series Klincus and Dinomite

Junior Animator

UA School | September 2021 - July 2022

- Coordinator and animator of the 3D project based on the film "We are the Millers"
- Animation of a spider for a videogame called Meir
- Animation of a knight for a videogame called Dark Dungeon.

Education

Universal Arts School

Máster in 3D Character animation | 2020 - 2022

Universidad de Burgos

Degree in Audiovisual Comunication | 2015 - 2019

Academy curses

MasterCartoon

Animawarriors | Online

Pixar in a box

Khan Academy | Online

Software

- Maya: Advance.
- Blender: Basic.
- Premiere: Medium.
- Illustrator: MediumAfter Effects: Basic.
- Photoshop; Basic

Language

- Spanish: Native
- English: Advance C1
- German: Basic. A2



Sobre mi:

Soy una joven de 26 años que le apasiona la animación. Desde pequeña he querido crear y contar historias que traspasaran la pantalla. Quiero, no solo incrementar mis conocimientos y habilidades, si no también crecer como persona. Busco poder transmitir y compartir mis destrezas y aprender de las habilidades de los demás y es algo que el trabajo en equipo puede aportarme

Más información

- Carné de conducir tipo B
- Disponibilidad total

Contacto

+34 689 17 14 50

patriciaidoate@gmail.com

Q España

https://vimeo.com/758018160

PATRICIA IDOATE

Animadora 3D de personajes

Experiencia

Fixer Animator

Mago Production | Mayo 2024 - Actualidad

- Corregir y arreglar las animaciones de la película The light of Aisha
- Publicar y renderizar los planos de la película The light of Aisha

Fixer Animator

B-Water (Barcelona) | Febrero 2023 - Marzo 2024

- Corregir y arreglar las animaciones de las series de televisión Klincus y Dino-mite
- Publicar y renderizar los planos de la serie Klincus y Dino-mite

Junior Animator

UA School | Septiembre 2021 - Julio 2022

 Coordinadora y animadora de un proyecto 3D basado en la película "We are the Millers"

Educación

Enseñanzas profesionales Sorolla

Programación de videojuegos, diseño 3D y realidad virtual | 2023

Universal Arts School

Máster en animación de personajes 3D | 2020 - 2022

Universidad de Burgos

Grado en comunicación audiovisual | 2015 - 2019

Cursos Académicos

Pantomima Cartoon

Animawarriors and Animbot | Online

Software

- Maya: Avanzado
- Blender: Básico
- **Premiere**: Intermedio
- Illustrator: Intermedio
- After Effects: Básico
- Photoshop; Básico

Idiomas

- Español: Nativo
- Inglés: Avanzado C1
- Alemán: Básico A2